Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dailies, Circa 1985 - 2010; Series 13
  - Dailies, 1988 May 18; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 112)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 19; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 113)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 20; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 114)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 21; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 115)
  - Docent Luncheon, 1988 May 23; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 116)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 23; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 117)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 24; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 118)
  - Reception at Foxley Leach Gallery, 1988 May 24; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 119)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 26; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 120)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 30; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 121)
  - Dailies, 1988 May 31; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 122)
  - Dailies, 1988 June 1; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 123)
  - Dailies, 1988 June 2; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 124)
  - Dailies, 1988 June 3; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 125)
  - Dailies, 1988 June 4; Series 13 (Box 28, Folder 126)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 6; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 9; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 10; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 11; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 12; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 13; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 14; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 16; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 17; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 19; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 23; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 24; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 25; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 26; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 27; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Dailies, 1984 April 30; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Dailies, 1984 May; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 3; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 4; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 5; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 6; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 7; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 9; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 10; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 11; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 12; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 14; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 15; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 16; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 17; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 18; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 21; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 23; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 24; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 30; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Dailies, 1984 May 31; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Dailies, 1984 June; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 2; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 4; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 6; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 7; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 11; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 12; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 13; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 15; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 16; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 17; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 18; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 19; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 20; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 21; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 25; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 28; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Dailies, 1984 June 29; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Dailies, 1984 July; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Dailies, 1984 July 2; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Dailies, 1984 July 12; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Dailies, 1984 July 13; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Dailies, 1984 July 19; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Dailies, 1984 July 23; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Dailies, 1984 July 26; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Staff Meeting Notes, 1982; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Corporate Membership Information sent - no date specified, 1984; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Dailies, 1983; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence September 1983, 1984 September; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence October 1983, 1983 October; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - Memos 1983, Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence, 1983 December; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence February 1984, 1984 February; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence February 1984, 1984 February; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence March 1984, 1984 March; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence 1984, Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence June 1984, 1984 June; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - Memos Current Attendance Report, 1985; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - Musical Evening Series, 1984-1985; Series 13 (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - Dailies, 1992 March; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1992 March; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 2; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 3; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 4; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 6; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 9; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 13; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 14; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 16; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 19; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 20; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 21; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 22; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 23; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 24; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 25; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 28; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 29; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Wesleyan/Brown Memorial Lecture, 1992 March 29; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Dailies, 1992 March 30; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Dailies, 1992 April; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 3; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 4; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 7; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 8; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 9; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 10; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 12; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Picturing History Press Kit, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Summer Sessions: Jazz at the Corcoran T-Shirt Money, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - David's House, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Jazz Tony Matarrese, 1992 December 2; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran, 1994; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Jazz, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Jazz Groups, 1991; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Summer Sessions PR, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Jazz Gospel Brunches, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Entertainment: Classical Guitar Michael Kolmstetter, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Jazz/Whit Williams Quintet, 1992 September 16; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Jazz - Harold Howland Quartet, 1992 September 23; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - George Hummel Quartet, 1992 September 9; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Steve Jordon Trio, 1992 September 2; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Marty Nau Quartet, 1992 August 5; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Mike Davis Quintet, 1992 August 12; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Dave Steinmeyer Quintet, 1993 August 26; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - Jazz - Vaughn Nark Quintet, 1992 October 7; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - Loose, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Jack Wolfe Quintet, 1992 August 19; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - Maurice Robertson Quartet Jazz at the Corcoran, 1992 November 4; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - David Marsh Quintet - Jazz, 1992 November 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran Harry Bass and his Quartet, 1992 October 28; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 54)
  - Dailies, 1992 October 19; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 55)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Ray Dempsey, 1992 Octobber 21; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 56)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran Dick Morgan Quartet, 1991 October 9; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 57)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: John Eaton, 1991 November 13; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 58)
  - Summer Sessions: Jazz at the Corrcoran Andrew White Quartet, 1991 August 7; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 59)
  - Summer Sessions: Jazz at the Corcoran Jack Wolfe Quintet, 1991 August 14; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 60)
  - Summer Sessions? Jazz at the Corcoran Ernie Douglas Quartet, 1991 August 21; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 61)
  - Summer Sessions: Jazz at the Corcoran Brooks Tegler Quartet, 1991 August 28; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 62)
  - Buck Hill Quartet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 63)
  - Summer Sessions; Jazz at the Corcoran Lennie Cuje Quartet, 1991 September 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 64)
  - Summer Sessions: Jazz at thee Corcoran Keter Betts Quartet, 1991 September 18; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 65)
  - Jazz Flyers and Expenses, Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 66)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Joe Rinaldi Quartet, 1992 January 15; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 67)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Tony Martucci Quartet, 1992 January 29; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 68)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Peter Robinson, 1992 February 5; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 69)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Roland Young Quartet, 1992 February 12; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 70)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Daryle Davis Quintet, 1992 October 14; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 71)
  - Jazz Series Bills, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 72)
  - Special Events Roundtable, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 73)
  - Karen Devitt Quintet, 1992 September 30; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 74)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Scheduules of Concerts, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 75)
  - Jazz - The Ron Holloway Group, 1992 November 18; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 76)
  - Jazz: Vince Patterson, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 77)
  - Summer Sessions; Jazz at the Corcoran Ron Elliston Quartet, 1991 July 31; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 78)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Gus Sims Quartet, 1992 June 17; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 79)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Ron Elliston Quartet, 1992 July 29; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 80)
  - Jazz at the Corcorarn - Dick Morgan Quartet, 1992 June 24; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 81)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Buck Hill Quartet, 1992 July 1; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 82)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran -- Harrold Summey Quintet, 1992 July 8; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 83)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Brooks Tegler Quartet, 1992 July 15; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 84)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Davey Yarborough Quartet, 1992 July 22; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 85)
  - Jazz Flyer, 1991 July - 1991 September; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 86)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: John Ozment, 1992 February 26; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 87)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Art Dawkins Quartet, 1992 May 20; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 88)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Gabriel Meadows Quartet, 1992 March 4; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 89)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Clyde Dickerson Quartet, 1992 March 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 90)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: David Kanes Quartet, 1992 March 18; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 91)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: John Cusick Quartet, 1992 March 25; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 92)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Ted Efantis Quintet, 1992 April 1; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 93)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: John Cunliffe Quartet, 1992 April 15; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 94)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Chris Vadala Quartet, 1992 April 29; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 95)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: John Cocuzzi Quartet, 1992 June 3; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 96)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Adolph Qright Quartet, 1992 June 10; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 97)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: George Spika Quartet, 1991 October 1; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 98)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: John Jenkins Trio, 1991 October 16; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 99)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Tony Matarrese Trio, 1991 October 24; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 100)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Stan Rouse Quartet, 1992 January 22; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 101)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Jazz Street Station, 1991 October 2; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 102)
  - Jazz Poster, 1992-1993; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 103)
  - Crotty O'Neill Quintet, 1991 October 30; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 104)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Eddie Phyfe Quintet, 1991 November 6; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 105)
  - Summer Sessions: Jazz at the Corcoran: Keter Betts Quartet, 1991 July 17; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 106)
  - Summer Session: Jazz at the Corcoran: Dick Morgan Quartet, 1991 July 24; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 107)
  - Music Performance Trust Fund/DC Federation of Musicians, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 108)
  - Schedule for Jazz Series, 1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 109)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran - Students from Howard University, 1992 April 8; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 110)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Mark Behabetz Quartet, 1992 April 22; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 111)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Calvin Jones Quartet, 1992 May 13; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Charlie Byrd Quartet, 1992 May 27; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 113)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Damon Foreman Quartet, 1992 May 6; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 114)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Charlie Hampton Quintet, 1992 February 19; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 115)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Ron Kramer Quartet, 1991 November 20; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 116)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Tom Teasley Trio, 1991 November 27; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 117)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Ron Kramer Quartet, 1991 November 20; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 118)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Reuben Brown Trio, 1991 December 4; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 119)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Charlie Barden, 1991 December 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 120)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Maurice Lyles Quintet, 1992 January 8; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 121)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 10; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 122)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 13; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 123)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 14; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 124)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 16; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 125)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 17; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 126)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 18; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 127)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 20; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 128)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 21; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 129)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 23; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 130)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 25; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 131)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 26; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 132)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 29; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 133)
  - Dontemporary Music Forum, 1992-1993; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 134)
  - Washington Chamber Symphony, 1992-1994; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 135)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 1993-1994; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 136)
  - Corcoran Chamber Festival: American Chamber Players, 1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 137)
  - American Chamber Players, 1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 138)
  - American Chamber Players Concert, 1992 June 4; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 139)
  - American Chamber Players Concert, 1992 June 11; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 140)
  - American Chamber Players Concert, 1992 June 18; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 141)
  - American Chamber Players Concert, 1992 June 25; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 142)
  - Jazz at the Corcoran: Dave Burns Quartet, 1991 September 25; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 143)
  - Corcoran Jazz Series, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 144)
  - Jazz Bios, 1991; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 145)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 31; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 146)
  - Dailies, 1992 February; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 147)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 2; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 3; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 149)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 5; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 150)
  - Dailies, 1992 February 7; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 151)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 13; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 152)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 14; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 153)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 16; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 154)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 18; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 155)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 19; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 156)
  - Dailies, 1992 April 20; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 157)
  - Dailies, 1991 December 31; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 158)
  - Dailies, 1992 January; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 159)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 8; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 160)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 19; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 161)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 14; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 162)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 16; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 163)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 17; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 164)
  - Director's Evenign Reception, 1992 January 21; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 165)
  - Washington Chamber Symphony, Circa 1991-1992; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 166)
  - Dailies, 1992 Janaury 28; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 167)
  - Dailies, 1992 January 30; Series 13 (Box 48, Folder 168)
  - Dailies, 1993 May; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 1; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 2; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 3; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 5; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 7; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 8; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 9; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 10; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 11; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 12; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Commencement 1993, Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 15; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 16; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 17; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 18; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 19; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 21; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Dailies, 1993 May 28; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 1; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 1; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 1; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Fitzgerald / Saul Dinner, Circa 1993; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 2; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 4; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 5; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 7; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 8; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 9; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 14; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 16; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 19; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 20; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 21; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 22; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 23; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 24; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 26; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Rescuers, 1993 June 28; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 29; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Dailies, 1993 June 30; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Dailies, 1993 July; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 4; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 8; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 9; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 11; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 14; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 15; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 15; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 24; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 26; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Dailies, 1993 July 29; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Dailies, 1993 August; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 3; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 9; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 11; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 12; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 20; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 21; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 27; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - Dailies, 1993 August 28; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - Dailies, 1993 September; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 2; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 3; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 64)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 7; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 65)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 9; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 66)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 10; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 67)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 11; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 68)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 12; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 69)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 13; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 70)
  - Ford / Visions VIP, Circa 1993; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 71)
  - Latin American Folk Art Opening, Circa 1993; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 72)
  - Luncheon, 1993 September 14; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 73)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 17; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 74)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 18; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 75)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 19; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 76)
  - Dailies, 1993 September 20; Series 13 (Box 49, Folder 77)
  - IBM Invitation List, Circa 1993-1994; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1994 January 28; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1994 January 29; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1994 January 31; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1994 February; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - ISES Meeting, 1994 February 1; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 2; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Winter Opening, 1994 February 4; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 7; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 8; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 8; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 12; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 14; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 16; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Dailies, 1994 February 17; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - School Ball, 1994 February 18; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Family Day, 1994 February 19; Series 13 (Box 50, Folder 17)